Hey Hello Guys the other guy Ankur Upadhyay
welcome to our channel Stock Market Analysis
Nice talkers TCS daily there has been a big fall in the stock of Tata
Consultancy Services Limited
till today it had fallen with the entire IIT in the
morning and the reason for the fall is
known to all of you very well because of the weak results
but the question arises that this stock was
seen by a lot of public carry forward
why after the results that came in this way,
somewhere or the other the result will go up within that unit
and a good rise is being
seen
so every person's position is thinking that TCS and
commission have
subscribed to TCS Infosys Wipro HCL Tech
but somewhere or the other everything will recover but if
someone made a particular position in TCS
before the result then he is somewhere
in loss but after this what should be
its strategy or see somewhere or the other it is the
market leader TC, you all
know that in this fall now is the
opportunity to buy or should we deploy a little more
how far can the shares go what could be the
target and what is the big  News, we will
talk about all this, so let's do a video guys,
before starting, let me tell you if
you have any stone related to this, you
want to talk to me, then I am
on Instagram ID Pandit Brothers, you
can talk to me, see, first of all I would
like to give an update, in Friday's session,
by recommending 360 to all of you in the Senate,
which was my first target of quality end, from
that front part Informatica the
biggest, somewhere the stock is achieving the first target
very well,
360, three percent rise in one day, a second target of
1520 near highway stock, so somewhere almost dead,
four percent rise in one day, a
very big thing, near our line,
finance, this top, if you also
want to join us on this topic, then you
can tell me by messaging me on my dad, I will
talk about the history, if you
look at TCS according to today's points, then there is a
big fall of 215 points, if you
go into percentage, then that big fall is
5.5 percent of the stock in the morning
That I have completely come
down with the market, it is very powerful to
clean the market and this down in the market like this,
because of this
in the market I will tell you that
today's opening
guest of TCS has
recovered at 62 cents, okay,
Infosys's
60 car
Hussain stock has recovered, that is, IT only,
put the market from bottom to top, the market was in
regulatory fifty-sixty these in the morning,
but that is because of IIT, IT has gone up,
oil ad Infosys has become green,
Asian is trading at 1617 and its
Lohri festival was
given 55-75 percent, now Punjab has become completely
flat, so somewhere the entire IT
opened negative like 45 cents and
somewhere all the recovery is there except TCS, the
result of TCS is there, now the question arises that
whoever has a position in TCS should do
deliveries, okay do
not enter it at all, whatever was to happen has happened, the
reaction was to come of the results has come, the
stock has fallen by five percent, according to me,
stay in the position because if you exit then
you  Due to the 100 point relative price of 2.5
% and the last, you will
book a loss of 5-7%. And according to me,
you have to reverse your strategy now. You have been
sitting quietly for 3 months and wait for the
next result.
You will see the stock calling out. You will
see the result was excellent but weaker than expected.
After the central results, the market was
predicting very
good results. Almost
our expectations were very high, so
somewhere in
comparison to that, the stock presented a slight comeback result,
which you saw in Rani Store. There is a
big fall. Now the
stock is ending at 3723. Now you should
not cut the position at all. If you are looking for an upside
but buy, then see, according to me,
investors who are in a position are positional
traders. Traders all get trapped somewhere or the other. So, I
mean this stock set.
But the position operators who might be
afraid of a big fall in this, then
I want to tell them that your fear is over.
Now what you have to do is
fold the position. 3 months  Minimum 3
months, minimum take maximum 3
months, you should be in your position,
stop looking around and this is increasing, that is increasing, I have to
buy this, that is increasing, I will sell this and take it, friend,
when will I do it, leave all
this, you have put your trust in TCS,
trust me, wait for 3 months, wait for
your launch, you will go somewhere else to cover 4
%, 5% and even more
scams, in the process of covering many more,
so stay here, maximum dance of 860
3550 is a very strong, very strong
base, I am not keeping it, if there is a break, then
see, from here 300 points from here, the
correction has already happened, now there you will fall by 100 points or
more, but you will get upset
again because
brokerage houses are talking too much on device stocks,
after such results, let me tell you,
HDFC Securities target ad, Tata
Consultancy Services target 180 per person
target, after that you will see that the maximum
target of 44 century according to junior out, today
I think the targets of brokerage houses will be seen coming.  There is absolutely nothing to be afraid of.
Watch the stock for 3 months. If you
think that I have made a profit of
9% and then I will go for another record, then you are absolutely right in thinking. But if you have bought it well, then do not search for TCS, its name is Tata Consultancy Services. Why is there anything to be afraid of? It has fallen by 4%, so what happened? Stay
in position.
Your 45% will be recovered. It may
take time to make a profit,
but it is advisable to fold on the quarter.
Now talking to friends, to make a difference entry,
you have to wait that the stock
reaches
3738, okay. Almost two to two and a half percent has been corrected, it has been
recovered. Okay, now
you have to wait. Therefore, you will get the stock of this six,
you will not get it like this. The recovery that has come will
change again or I will also get it
twice in the last hour. Next day for baby boy, Jha will come below 3078.
You should understand it as if you are
buying it little by little, you have bought a poison dipper.  You will be
able to send certificate third tips in this third specific strict
stuffing like this I do
n't think it will come at all and that is the method
your target which will be third in Noida end will be equal to do
first crossing the forces then buy the
stock slowly presented do
not buy it immediately do
not buy it at all
results are yet to come in IIT also whatever the big ones have done a little
then more will come slowly Infosys
HCL Tech Mahindra Wipro all will do it
now slowly every compartment has to be done
completely Yogi According to me for you
strategy in TCS and whatever is in the launch it should remain a complete
break up but
for 30 years it is a great stop very great company
and they have done a lot of their work there is
no problem stay tuned yes yes it has
been corrected people
's expectations are high its two good so
you all must have liked that understanding on TCS share so thank
you so much for watching this video